[
    {
        "id":0,
        "question": "Q1) Find the greatest number that will divide 43, 91 and 183 so as to leave the same remainder in each case. ",
        "options":[
            "A) 4",
            "B) 7",
            "C) 9",
            "D) 13"

        ],
        "answer":"A) 4"
    },
    {
        "id":1,
        "question": "Q2) Which of the following fraction is the largest ?  ",
        "options":[
           "A) 7/8", 
            "B) 13/16",
            "C) 31/40",
            "D) 63/80"
       ],
        "answer":"A) 7/8"
    },{
        "id":2,
        "question": "Q3) Find the greatest number that will divide 43, 91 and 183 so as to leave the same remainder in each case. ",
        "options":[
            "A) 4",
            "B) 7",
            "C) 9",
            "D) 13"

        ],
        "answer":"A) 4"
    },{
        "id":3,
        "question": "Q4) The least perfect square, which is divisible by each of 21, 36 and 66 is: ",
        "options":[
            "A) 213444",
            "B) 214344",
            "C) 214434",
            "D) 213454"
        ],
        "answer":"A) 213444"
    },{
        "id":4,
        "question": "Q5) If 20% of a = b, then b% of 20 is the same as: ",
        "options":[
            "A) 4% of a",
            "B) 5% of a",
            "C)20% of a",
            "D) None of these"
        ],
        "answer":"A) 4% of a"
    },{
        "id":5,
        "question": "Q6) A man walked diagonally across a square lot. Approximately, what was the percent saved by not walking along the edges? ",
        "options":[
            "A) 20",
            "B) 24",
            "C) 30",
            "D) 33"

        ],
       "answer":"C) 30"
    },{
        "id":6,
        "question": "Q7) Find the odd man out. 10, 25, 45, 54, 60, 75, 80 ",
        "options":[
            "A) 10",
            "B) 45",
            "C) 54",
            "D) 75"

        ],
        "answer":"C) 54"
    },{
        "id":7,
        "question": "Q8) Find the greatest number that will divide 43, 91 and 183 so as to leave the same remainder in each case. ",
        "options":[
            "A) 4",
            "B) 7",
            "C) 9",
            "D) 13"

        ],
        "answer":"A) 4"
    },{
        "id":8,
        "question": "Q9) 582, 605, 588, 611, 634, 617, 600 ",
        "options":[
            "A) 634",
            "B) 611",
            "C) 605",
            "D) 600"

        ],
        "answer":"A) 634"
    },{
        "id":9,
        "question": "Q10) 8, 24, 12, 36, 18, 54, (....) ",
        "options":[
            "A) 27",
            "B) 108",
            "C) 68",
            "D) 72"

        ],
        "answer": "A) 27"

    }
]
 


